yourhotcar.com 2012-11-23

# Crown Victoria - Buy Ford Crown Victoria

**YourHotCar.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate the firm commitment to the privacy of visitors and customers. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the website: **YourHotCar.com**

**Sharing and Usage**  
**How can you stop receiving email from us?**  
**User Agreement**

**How we protect your privacy**

**IP Addresses**  
IP addresses are used to help diagnose problems related to server operations. IP addresses are also used to help identify customers, their respective shopping carts and to gather broad demographic information.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are used to keep track of shopping cart activity and to deliver information customized to respective customer interests. A cookie is stored only on the customer's respective computer and does not contain any credit card, address, or other personal information. The cookies are not shared with any other company.

**Information Use**  
Individual contact, registration, order, contest, survey and other information collected online from users (including name, address, email, telephone, demographic, vehicle) will not be sold, rented or provided to third parties for any type of use. , Inc. reserves the right to use this information to send its users company related information or promotional material. Users are afforded a clear opportunity to opt-out of any email list as outlined in the email privacy policy:  

> **E- mail Privacy Policy**  
>  This email privacy policy has been created to demonstrate .com firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.
> 
> **Why did you receive an email from us?**  
>  If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.
> 
> **How we protect your privacy**  
>  We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.
> 
> **Sharing and Usage**  
>  We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.
> 
> **How can you stop receiving email from us?**  
>  Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email.

**User Agreement**  
A customer's use of this site and/or placement of an order indicates acceptance of terms and conditions. reserves the right to make changes to the website and its terms and conditions at any time without notice.
